Hello.
In this next lecture, we're going to go over how to create a moving source.
It's going to behave very similarly to our moving platform.
Except if our player, character or our enemy touches it, that will come damaged.
To get started, go over to our item image folder and then close on our engine and drag in the source
image.
It will be attached in the course lecture.
Then if we apply paper to the texture settings to this and extract these sprites.
Under sprite extract mode, go grid and change the cell width to be 38.
Then if we let all these sprites.
And go create flipbook.
And I'm going to name this my sole.
And then if we head over to the item photo, right click on the immune platform and go duplicate and
call this our saw underscore BP.
If we open it up, we can delete everything inside of the event graph.
And go up to the viewport and we can delete the paper, sprite and the box.
Now we're just left with the interactive movement component.
If we go ahead and look for a paper flipbook.
And if we just look for the saw flipbook that we just made.
And I'm going to scale it up a bit.
Something like five.
And I'm going to go ad and look for sphere collision.
And make it fair.
And also.
Then if we scroll down and go to one component, we can overlap when anything overlaps.
So we're going to drive off here and look for apply damage.
And we're going to do one damage.
We can compile, save and close this.
Now, if I drag in my soul and move it to layer 20 in the Y.
I'm going to make my swing move up and down.
And let's give it a speed of three.
So now if I go play now, let's say I jump into the saw, I will become damaged.
Nice.